// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is lead vocalist of the band Coldplay?",
    answer: "Chris Martin",
    options: [
    "Chris Martin",
        "Chris Brown",
        "Chris Connelly ",
        "Chris Wallace"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which singer was featured in Jack&U (Skrillex & Diplo) 2015 song Where R U Now?",
    answer: "Justin Bieber",
    options: ["Selena Gomez",
    "Ellie Goulding",
    "Justin Bieber",
    "The Weeknd"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which was Zayn Malik's debut album as a solo artist?",
  
    answer: "Mind Of Mine",
    options: [
      
        "Icarus Falls",
        "Mind Of Mine",
        "Nobody Is Listening",
        "Up All Night"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is the singer of the hit track Little Red Corvette?",
    
    answer: "Prince",
    options: [
     
        "Usher",
        "Michael Jackson",
        "Prince",
        "Marvin Gaye"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "With which rapper did Ariana Grande collaberate in her song The Way?",
    
    answer: "Mac Miller",
    options: [
      
        "Megan Thee Stallion",
        "Machine Gun Kelly",
        "Eminem",
        "Mac Miller"
    ]
  },
  

     {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Which song is Zayn Malik's highest charted single as a solo artist till date?",
     
     answer: "Pillowtalk",
     options: [
      "I Don't Wanna Live Forever",
      "Pillowtalk",
      "Let Me",
      "Dusk Till Dawn"
     ]
   },
     {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Which Taylor Swift album is Blank Space on?",
     
     answer: "1989",
     options: [
      
        "Taylor Swift",
        "Speak Now",
        "Red",
        "1989"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which artist is the lead singer and guitarist for the indie rock band The 1975?",
      
      answer: "Matthew Healy",
      options: [
        "Matthew Healy",
        "Marvin Gaye",
        "Marren Morris",
        "Harry Styles"
      ]
    },
      {
      numb: 9,
      question: "In which video does Michael Jackson plays a zombie?",
      
      answer: "Thriller",
      options: [
        
        "Thriller",
        "Bad",
        "Beat It",
        "Hollywood Tonight"
       ]
     },
     {
      numb: 10,
      question: "In which Jonas Brothers video did actress Camilla Belle was featured?",
      
      answer: "Love Bug",
      options: [
        
        "Love Bug",
        "Paranoid",
        "Burnin' Up",
        "Jealous"
       ]
     },
];